 <root>
	 
 	<story>
		<story_id>21</story_id>
		<story_title>The Man Who Could not Die</story_title>
 		<story_des><![CDATA[Eos, Goddess of Dawn fell in love with a youth named Tithonius, and the two spent many happy years together. But while Eos being a goddess retained her youth, Tithonius began to age. He asked his beloved to grant him immortality. She couldn’t do it on her own so she pleaded his case with Zeus, the supreme deity. 
 		Zeus reluctantly granted the boon.The story unfortunately does not have a happy ending. Tithonius had forgotten to ask for eternal youth. So though he could not die he could age. As his age advanced he became wrinkled and hunchbacked and revoltingly ugly. He pleaded with Eos to help him. 
		 She could not take back the gift of immortality nor could she give him back his youth. But she could change his form. She turned him into a grasshopper. ]]></story_des>
 	</story>
 	 
 	<story>
		<story_id>22</story_id>
		<story_title>The God of Love </story_title>
 		<story_des><![CDATA[Eros was the son of Aphrodite, goddess of love, and was always at her side to assist her in her matchmaking endeavors. 
 		He was a blond and playful winged youth, armed with a golden bow and arrows. Whoever he shot at immediately fell in love. 
 		One day Aphrodite, jealous of the beauty of the earthly princess, Psyche, ordered her son to make the princess fall in love with the ugliest man on earth. Eros set out to do his mothers bidding, but when he saw Psyche fell in love with her himself. 
 		He began to visit her every night, but afraid of his mothers wrath, always remained in the shadows, to conceal his identity. 
 		One night while he was asleep, Psyche lit an oil lamp in order to get a look at his face. But her hand trembled and a drop of hot oil fell on the god, awakening him. Angry and frightened, he made himself invisible and went away, never to return. 
 		But the two pined for each other and eventually Zeus, the king of gods, intervened to bring them together again. 
 		Psyche was taken to Mount Olympus, the abode of the gods, and there she became revered as the personification of the human soul. 
 		Later, when the Romans imported Greek gods into their pantheon, Eros became Cupid and though he remained the god of love he was not given as much importance as the Greeks had given Eros. 
 		Cupid was usually shown blindfolded, perhaps to indicate that he chose his victims at random. In later art Cupid was shown as a small cherubic winged boy armed with a bow and arrow. ]]></story_des>
 	</story>
 	 
	</root>